#### susantshrestha@hotmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/susantstha49

Website: <a href="https://iamsusant.github.io">https://iamsusant.github.io</a>

Mobile: 9808883404 / 9840174922

Naxal, Kathmandu

Nepal

## SUSANT SHRESTHA

#### **SUMMARY**

My work is driven by a single goal: crafting delightful experiences through a combination of user-centered research, streamlined workflow processes and openminded iterative collaboration.

Around two years of experience in planning, requirement analysis, design, and developing a web application. Experience with design patterns, Object Oriented Systems Design. Able to work in both team and self-directed environment with quick learning and mastering new technology.

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML5,nunjucks,handlebar
- CSS3,Sass
- · JavaScript, JQuery
- Vue js ,React js
- Gulp
- Webpack
- Data visualization

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## FRONTEND UI DEVELOPER, AMNIL TECHNOLOGY

2020-PRESENT

**Overall Responsibilities** 

- A level of design and business understanding so as to not compromise on business goals and design intents
- Stick to established coding standards and group procedures individually and in teams.
- Plan and estimate projects and reports hours to administration for billing.
- Create conceptual diagrams, visual mockups and manage detailed user interface specifications.
- Guide and maintain developer teams and best practices.

### 2018 - 2020

## **Overall Responsibilities**

- Planning, analyzing and designing web application according to client specification
- Collaborate with other platform developers following engineering standards and best practice
- Develop clean, elegant , well-commented and reusable code which is maintain and extend ensure quality

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER, FREELANCE

#### 2016-2018

- Overall Responsibilities
- Deliver project according to client requirements

EDUCATION	BACHELOR'S IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING 2016
	Advanced College of Engineering & Management, Kathmandu, Nepal
SOCIAL ACCOUNT	linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/susantstha49
WEBSITE	https://iamsusant.github.io/
REFERENCES	ER.RITESH GHIMIRE SENIOR PROGRAMMER
	KANTIPUR DIGITAL CORP
	9849281471

**ER.PURUSHOTTAM BAGALE** TELECOM ENGINEER

NEPAL TELECOM

9851111129

Page | 2 susant shrestha